George S. McGovern Papers Series 5: Audiovisual Materials, 1957-1984 (bulk 1968-1972 )
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 5: Audiovisual Materials, 1957-1984; 105.42 linear feet 110 boxes Approximately 1,785 items
  - Subseries 5B, 1960 January 20-1969 December 17; 14.5 linear feet 14 boxes
    - 1968 Campaign Speeches, undated; 1016; 1 box (Box 796)
    - McGovern half hour, 1968; 475; 16mm 1 box (Box 890)
    - Rural Electric Association Loan Authorization, 1968 May 1; 554; 1 box (Box 796)
    - McGovern and Kennedy Spots, 1968 May 10-11; 1968 May 29; 1160; 1 box (Box 796)
    - Senators Robert Kennedy, Ted Kennedy, George McGovern, 1968 May 10-29; portion of 1 box (Box 796)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 376, 388.
    - Tourism in South Dakota, 1968 May 14; 333; 1 box (Box 796)
    - San Diego State University Radio, 1968 May 24; 941; 1 box (Box 796)
    - Senator Ted Kennedy, WNAX Interview, 1968 May 29; portion of 1 box (Box 796)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 327, 330.
    - Agriculture, Vietnam, Military Establishment, 1968 June; 1447; 1 box (Box 796)
    - Senator Karl Mundt Radio Broadcast, 1968 June 4; 1765; 1 box (Box 796)
    - CBS News, 1968 June 6; 50; 2-inch 1 box (Box 797)
      This item has been transferred to DVD.
    - Address at Elmhurst College, Elmhurst, Illinois, 1968 February 26; 387; 1 box (Box 798)
    - Dr. Gustav Landmann-McGovern Endorsement, 1968 April 7; 1029; 1 box (Box 798)
    - Food for Peace Program, World Council of Churches, 1968 July 5; 1706-1718; 1 box (Box 798)
    - World Council of Churches, Food for Peace Program, 1968 July 7; 1721-1724; 1 box (Box 798)
    - Kennedy Memorial Dinner, 1968 July 13; 331; 1 box (Box 798)
    - Democratic State Convention, Huron, South Dakota, 1968 July 14; 1686; 16mm 1 box (Box 798)
    - World Council of Churches, 1968 July 15; 1 box (Box 798)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 351, 355, 358-360, 1017.
    - 1968 July 15, 1410; 1 box (Box 798)
    - Candidacy Announcement, 1968 August 15; 1008; 1 box (Box 798)
    - Nominee at Democratic Convention, 1968 August 26; 1007; 1 box (Box 798)
    - Democratic Convention-California Caucus, 1968 August 26-30; 1012; 1 box (Box 798)
    - Speech to California Caucus at 1968 Convention, 1968 August 26-30; 1013-1014; 1 box (Box 798)
    - 1968 August 29, 1468; 1 box (Box 798)
    - 1968 Democratic National Convention, 1968 September 24; 1039; 1 box (Box 798)
    - Aberdeen Chamber of Commerce, 1968 October 9; 1025; 1 box (Box 798)
    - NBC TV, 1968 October 10; 1038; 1 box (Box 798)
    - South Dakota Education Assignment, 1968 October 11; 597; 1 box (Box 798)
    - Radio Spots, 1968 October 16; 939; 1 box (Box 798)
    - U.S. Senate, 1968 October 17; 695; 1 box (Box 798)
    - McGovern for Senate, Cuts #1-4, 1968 October 22; 1151; 1 box (Box 799)
    - Keogh Interview, 1968 October 23; 922; 1 box (Box 799)
    - 1968 Senatorial Campaign Spots, 1968 October 23; 1026; 1 box (Box 799)
    - Edward Kennedy Spots for 1968 Senatorial Campaign, 1968 October 23; 1031; 1 box (Box 799)
    - Radio Spots #1-11, 1968 October 28; 60 seconds (Box 799)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 930-934, 937, 940, 951-952, 954, 956-957.
    - 60 and 20, Paper Ballot, 1968 October 29; 929; 1 box (Box 799)
    - McGovern for Senate Old Lady, 1968 October 30; 60 seconds 16mm color) (Box 799)
      Includes materials with identifiers: 484, 488, 511, 535, 730.
    - 4:40 pm Tape, 1968 November 3; 938; 13 minutes 30 seconds (Box 799)
    - Indian Program, 1968 November 3; 955; 1 box (Box 799)
    - David Susskind Show Tape and Justice Hugo Black, 1968 December 1-3; 1009; 1 box (Box 799)
    - Address to National Board of Americans for Democratic Action, 1968 December 7; 1032; 1 box (Box 799)
    - Huntley-Brinkley Report, 1968 December 17; 1033; 1 box (Box 799)
    - Georgetown University Forum, Hunger Abroad and U.S. Food: Wat's the Problem?, 1968 December 20; 352; 1 box (Box 799)
    - News Broadcast, 1968 December 21; 1036; 1 box (Box 799)
    - Meet the Press, 1968 December 29; 1020; 1 box (Box 799)
    - Meet the Press, 1968 December 29; 1760; 1 box (Box 800)
    - TV, 1969 January 28; 1042; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Frank Blair, Today Show, 1969 February 3; 1040; 1 box (Box 801)
    - McGovern on Vietnam, 1969 February 3-5; 1011; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Democratic Party Reform, 1969 February 6; 1041; 1 box (Box 801)
    - 2 TV Spots, 1969 February 7; 1043; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Daniel Shaw, CBS News, 1969 February 7; 1046; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Vietnam, 1969 February 23; 1027; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Hunger Program, 1969 March 19; 391; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Christian Crusade, Meridian, Ohio, 1969 April 23; 1037; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Hamburger Hill, 1969 May 31; 1477; 1 box (Box 801)
    - National Convention, 1969 July 1; 905; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Today, Hunger and BB Food, 1969 July 31; 1484; 1 box (Box 801)
    - CBS TV, 1969 September 20; 1478; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Schlesinger on McGovern, 1969 September 23; 369; 1 box (Box 801)
    - TV, 1969 October 1; 1481; 1 box (Box 801)
    - From Here to the 70s, 1969 October 7; 372; 1 box (Box 801)
    - CBS TV Spot, 1969 October 7; 1408; 1 box (Box 801)
    - NBC TV, George McGovern with Alan King, 1969 October 16; 381; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Lecture at Hudson Valley Community College, 1969 October 27; 602; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Buckley/Theodore White, 1969 November 9; 383; 1 box (Box 801)
    - McGovern Rally, 1969 November 15; 1044; 1 box (Box 801)
    - 1969 November 20, 1418; 1 box (Box 801)
    - Face The Nation, 1969 November 30; 385; 1 box (Box 801)
    - McGovern, 1969 December 1; 1479; 36 seconds (Box 801)
    - A Timetable for Vietnam, 1969 December 2; 1412; 1 box (Box 801)
    - McGovern on the David Frost Show, 1969 December 3; 382; 1 box (Box 801)
    - South Dakota Christmas Greeting Broadcast, 1969 December 17; 1023-1024; 1 box (Box 801)
  - Subseries 5C, 1970-1984 February 22; 30.4 linear feet 32 boxes
    This subseries documents McGovern's successful bid for the Democratic presidential nomination and his unsuccessful presidential campaign in 1972. In addition, it contains material on McGovern's 1974 Senate reelection campaign. Of particular interest are materials pertaining to the Amendment to End the War and President Nixon as well as McGovern's foreign travel for the Senate Committee on Foreign Relations.
    Subseries 5C is arranged chronologically.
    - 1970-1971, 1970-1972 January 4; portion of 154 boxes
      - McGovern Speech, Mitchell, South Dakota, 1970; 1364; 1 box (Box 801)
      - Service Club Speech, Huron, South Dakota, 1970 January 13; 608; 1 box (Box 801)
      - Democratic Dinner, 1970 January 13; 975; 1 box (Box 801)
      - National Press Club Luncheon, 1970 January 19; 959; 1 box (Box 801)
      - National Press Club, 1970 January 20; 958; 1 box (Box 801)
      - Dwight D. Eisenhower Inaugural Lecture, Wichita State University, 1970 February 9; 965; 1 box (Box 801)
      - Eisenhower Commission Report on Violence in U.S., 1970 February 10; 973; 1 box (Box 801)
      - Question and Answer Session, Kansas State College, 1970 February 10; 974; 1 box (Box 801)
      - Western States Democratic Conference, 1970 April 18; 976; 1 box (Box 801)
      - TV, 1970 April 24; 991; 1 box (Box 801)
      - TV, 1970 April 27; 990; 1 box (Box 801)
      - Food Assistance, 1970 April 27; 994; 1 box (Box 801)
      - WRC Interview, 1970 April 28; 810; 1 box (Box 801)
      - Recording of 60 minutes, Military Expenditures, 1970 May 6; 981; 1 box (Box 801)
      - Amendment to End the War, 1970 May 12; 75; 2-inch 1 box (Box 802)
      - Amendment to End the War, 1970 May 12; 1215; 1 box (Box 803)
      - Amendment to End the War, 1970 May 17; 74; 28 minutes 41 seconds 2-inch color) (Box 804)
      - Firing Line show #201, 1970 May 22; 32; 50mm 1 box (Box 874)
      - Sergeant Tod Hannes, U.S. Marine Intelligence, 1970 May 28; 371; 1 box (Box 805)
      - The Senate and the War, 1970 June 5; 970; 1 box (Box 805)
      - The Search for Peace Beyond Vietnam, Senior Symposia at Dartmouth College, New Hampshire, 1970 June 13; 1 box (Box 805)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 960, 1099, 1103-1104.
      - Issues, 1970 June 21; 971; 1 box (Box 805)
      - TV and Radio Spots, 1970 June 30; 1705; 13 minutes 5 Seconds (Box 805)
      - Postal Reform Bill Discussion, 1970 July 6; 516; 16mm 1 box (Box 805)
      - McGovern Profile, WNEW Radio, 1970 July 12; 967; 1 box (Box 805)
      - TV, 1970 July 20; 995; 1 box (Box 805)
      - Annual Banquet Address, SCLC Convention, Atlanta, Georgia, 1970 August 12; 968; 1 box (Box 805)
      - McGovern to SCLC, Atlanta, Georgia, 1970 August 12; 969; 1 box (Box 805)
      - 1970 August 17, 992; 1 box (Box 805)
      - TV, 1970 August 18; 989; 1 box (Box 805)
      - McGovern/Dole Issues and Answers, 1970 August 23; 966; 1 box (Box 805)
      - The Senate and the War on McGovern/Hatfield, 1970 August 29; 972; 1 box (Box 805)
      - Senators Fulbright and McGovern Discuss Indochina, 1970 August 31; 982; 1 box (Box 805)
      - Remarks for Defeat of Hatfield-McGovern Amendment, 1970 September 1; 997; 1 box (Box 805)
      - TV, 1970 September 11; 1006; 1 box (Box 805)
      - CBS TV, 1970 September 16; 1004; 1 box (Box 805)
      - Chicago, CBS TV, 6 pm, 1970 September 18; 993; 1 box (Box 805)
      - NBC TV, CBS TV, 1970 September 19; 988; 1 box (Box 805)
      - University of Oregon, Part I, 1970 September 23; 983; 1 box (Box 805)
      - TV, 1970 September 28; 999; 1 box (Box 805)
      - Capital Cloakroom, 1970 October 7; 963; 1 box (Box 805)
      - TV, 1970 October 8; 1000; 1 box (Box 805)
      - Anthony Scariano Dinner, Illinois Legislature Dinner, 1970 October 11; 962; 1 box (Box 805)
      - Page Auditorium, Duke University, Durham, North Carolina, 1970 October 28; 961; 1 box (Box 805)
      - TV, 1970 November 16; 1001; 1 box (Box 805)
      - State Dinner, 1970 November 16; 1469; 1 box (Box 805)
      - TV, 1970 November 19; 1002; 1 box (Box 805)
      - Radio, 1970 November 21; 1003; 1 box (Box 805)
      - 60 minutes and McGovern/Tower on Today, 1970 November 24; 964; 1 box (Box 805)
      - McGovern Cut from 60 Minutes, 1970 December 1; 57; 18 minutes 55 seconds 2-inch color) (Box 806)
      - TV, 1970 December 21-22; 998; 1 box (Box 807)
      - TV, 1970 December 22; 996; 1 box (Box 807)
      - TV, 1970 December 23; 1005; 1 box (Box 807)
      - Cavett TV Show, Bill Russell Guest House, 1970 December 4; 977; 1 box (Box 807)
      - McGovern in South Vietnam, 1971; 464; 16mm 1 box (Box 808)
      - TV, 1971; 842; 1 box (Box 809)
      - McGovern announcement, 1971 January 18; 33; 50mm 1 box (Box 875)
      - CBS TV, 1971 February 1; 824; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Cesar Chavez, Griffin TV, 1971 February 2; 816; 1 box (Box 809)
      - CBS TV, 1971 February 3; 825; 1 box (Box 809)
      - CBS/NBC, 1971 February 4; 826; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Issues and Answers, Muskie, 1971 February 7; 815; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Mrs. McGovern, 1971 February 7; 845; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Remarks on J.E. Hoover, 1971 February 10; 820; 1 box (Box 809)
      - TV, 1971 February 10; 827; 1 box (Box 809)
      - TV, 1971 February 11; 814; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Mike Douglas TV Show, 1971 February 12; 1055; 1 box (Box 809)
      - David Frost TV Show, 1971 February 16; 805; 1 box (Box 809)
      - 1971 February 18, 817; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Meet the Press and Washington Week, 1971 February 20-21; 804; 1 box (Box 809)
      - McGovern Student Union, 1971 February 21; 396; 1/2-inch 1 box (Box 809)
      - Interview N.H.N., 1971 February 25; 811; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Saint Anselm's College, 1971 February 26; 800; 1 box (Box 809)
      - McGovern TV News, 1971 February 26-27; 803; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Mrs. McGovern, 1971 March 1; 829; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Senator Jackson on McGovern, 1971 March 7; 802; 1 box (Box 809)
      - 1971 March 9, 844; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Philadelphia Town Meeting First and Second Half, 1971 March 18; 1057-1058; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Issues and Answers, 1971 March 21; 1060; 1 box (Box 809)
      - NBC TV and CBS TV, 1971 March 26; 813; 1 box (Box 809)
      - TV, 1971 April 3; 836; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Capitol Hill Today, 1971 April 20; 833; 1 box (Box 809)
      - TV, 1971 April 20; 835; 1 box (Box 809)
      - IndoChina-Another View, ABC TV, 1971 April 22; 807; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Book Beat, George Plimpton on RFK, 1971 April 26; 808; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Daniel-Times WQXR, Stamps, 1971 April 29; 819; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Howar/Susskind and Loyal Opposition, NBC TV, 1971 April 30-May 1; 1059; 1 box (Box 809)
      - 1971 May 3, 1074; 1 box (Box 809)
      - CBS Radio, NBC TV, 1971 May 8; 1075; 1 box (Box 809)
      - TV, 1971 May 16; 1091; 1 box (Box 809)
      - NBC TV, 1971 May 18; 1072; 1 box (Box 809)
      - 1971 May 20, 1085; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Hatfield, 1971 June 16; 801; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Hatfield, 1971 June 16; 839; 1 box (Box 809)
      - 1971 June 17, 832; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Today, 1971 June 18; 840; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Face the Nation and Washington Week, 1971 June 19-20; 1353; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Spot on McGovern Staff, TV News, Pentagon Study, 1971 June 20; 841; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Telephone Radio Show, 1971 July 12; 1382; 1 box (Box 809)
      - McGovern-Buzz, 1971 July 16; 809; 1 box (Box 809)
      - CBS TV, 1971 July 28; 838; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Address to National Welfare Rights Convention, 1971 July 29; 1052; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Radio/TV, 1971 August 8; 1083; 1 box (Box 809)
      - NBC TV, 1971 August 9; 1081; 1 box (Box 809)
      - TV, 1971 August 11; 1080; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Of the War, 1971 August 25; 831; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Washington Week, 1971 August 25; 843; 1 box (Box 809)
      - CBS Radio, 1971 August 28; 830; 1 box (Box 809)
      - TV, 1971 September 6; 837; 1 box (Box 809)
      - TV, 1971 September 14-15; 1082; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Crossfire, Part I- II, 1971 September 19; 1053-1054; 1 box (Box 809)
      - Someone Else, 1971 September 23; 1067; 1 box (Box 809)
      - TV, 1971 September 28; 1086; 1 box (Box 809)
      - ABC TV, 1971 September 30; 1087; 1 box (Box 809)
      - George McGovern, 1971 October 1; 56; 41 minutes 30 seconds 2-inch color) (Box 810)
      - 1971 October 2, 1079; 1 box (Box 811)
      - Face the Nation-John V. Lindsay, 1971 October 3; 1063; 1 box (Box 811)
      - TV, 1971 October 6; 1077; 1 box (Box 811)
      - TV, 1971 October 7; 1084; 1 box (Box 811)
      - Issues and Answers, ABC TV and Fred Harris on Meet the Press, 1971 October 10; 1048; 1 box (Box 811)
      - ABC TV, 1971 October 13; 1078; 1 box (Box 811)
      - CBS TV, 1971 October 17; 1068; 1 box (Box 811)
      - Troy, 1971 October 21; 1069; 1 box (Box 811)
      - Martin Agronsky: Evening Edition, 1971 October 25; 15; 28 minutes 30 seconds 2-inch (Box 812)
      - Evening Edition, WETA-TV, 1971 October 25; 1047; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Welfare Reform Bill, 1971 October 27; 1549; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Church Reception, Springfield, Massachusetts, 1971 October 31; 1050; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Salute to the States, 1971 November 2; 366; 1 box (Box 813)
      - CBS TV, 1971 November 2; 1089; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Today-McGovern NBC TV, 1971 November 5; 1065; 1 box (Box 813)
      - TV, 1971 November 9; 1088; 1 box (Box 813)
      - ABC TV, 1971 November 10; 1090; 1 box (Box 813)
      - 71-7 McGovern Student Center, Carbondale, Southern Illinois University, 1971 November 11; 278; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Speech, Question and Answer Reception, International Ian, 1971 November 11; 1049; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Florida Memorial, St. Augustine, 1971 November 12; 1061; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Young Men and Young Women's Association, 1971 November 14; 1062; 1 box (Box 813)
      - King of Prussia Plaza, 1971 November 15; 1467; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Political, 1971 November 16; portion of 1 box (Box 813)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 1177, 1257.
      - News Conference, Bullview-Stratford Hotel, Philadelphia, 1971 November 16; 1454; 1 box (Box 813)
      - TV, 1971 November 17; 1071; 1 box (Box 813)
      - McGovern, 1971 November 18; 169-171; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Vietnam: New Priorities, Amnesty, 1971 November 18; 1260; 1 box (Box 813)
      - AFL-CIO Convention, 1971 November 19; 606; 1 box (Box 813)
      - The Democrats-Loyal Opposition, 1971 November 21; 1066; 1 box (Box 813)
      - 71-7 McGovern Student Center, Carbondale, Southern Illinois University, 1971 November 30; 294; 1 box (Box 813)
      - East St. Louis, 1971 November 30; 1533; 1 box (Box 813)
      - CBS/ABC TV, 1971 December 1; 1076; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Democratic Dinner, Wisconsin, 1971 December 3; 1448; 1 box (Box 813)
      - CBS TV, 1971 December 9; 834; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Benjamin Franklin Dinner, New York City, 1971 December 9; 1535; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Department of Public Social Service, Los Angeles, California, 1971 December 14; 1445; 1 box (Box 813)
      - McGovern in Indochina, 1971 December 18; 1483; 50 seconds (Box 813)
      - NBC TV, 1971 December 19; 1482; 1 box (Box 813)
      - Washington Post Outlook Interview, 1971 December 22; portion of 1 box (Box 813)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 1465, 1466.
      - Polls and Campaign Funding, 1971 December 23; 1486; 1 box (Box 813)
      - GMPC, Washington, 1971 December 23; 1564; 1 box (Box 813)
      - TV; Muskie Speech, 1971 December 23; 1972 January 4; 1485; 1 box (Box 813)
    - 1972, portion of 379 boxes
      - McGovern '72: A Public Plan for Peace, 1972; ML.2017.017; portion of 1 box (Box 813)
        Filmstrip by Vietnam Slide Committee, McGovern Shriver 1972
      - 9 spots from '72 Campaign, 1972; 21; 2-inch 1 box (Box 813)
      - Spot #2-Inflation, 1972; 35; 5 minutes 2-inch (Box 813)
      - Telethon, 1972; 42; 2-inch 1 box (Box 813)
      - KXON, Mitchell, S.D. Spot #3-Special Interests, 1972; 43; 2-inch 1 box (Box 814)
      - McGovern Spots: Humphrey, Eleanor McGovern, Edward Kennedy, 1972; 450; 16mm 1 box (Box 814)
      - Black and White Negatives, 1972; 453; 16mm 1 box (Box 814)
      - McGovern Biography, 1972; 539; 16mm 1 box (Box 815)
      - Come Home America: A Candidate's Journey, 1972; 1786; ML.2014.020; 16mm 1 box (Box 940)
      - The Making of the President, Part 1, 1972; 584; portion of 1 box (Box 816)
      - The Making of the President, Part 2, 1972; 584; portion of 1 box (Box 816)
      - New Hampshire Campaign-Interviews with Citizens, 1972; 746-747; 1 box (Box 816)
      - New Hampshire Campaign, 1972; 748-749; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Eagleton-Miami, 1972; 1199; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Rural America, Reel #330, 1972; 1222; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Voter Registration Spots, 1972; 1235; 1 box (Box 816)
      - McGovern Radio-1972 Primary, 1239-1241; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Seventy-Two: There's a Big Change Coming, 1972; 1282; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Alameda County Fair, Labor Day, 1972; 1386; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Tallahassee Press Conference, 1972; 1637; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Fidel Castro, Sound Capsules, 1972; 1756; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Visit with Cesar Chavez: Phoenix, Arizona; Victory Statement: Portland, Oregon, 1972; 1757; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Statement, Election Night, Ohio Primary; Nebraska Primary Statement on Arrival in Omaha, Nebraska Airport; Press Conference; Q/A at Omaha Rally at High School, 1972; 1758; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Tape for McGovern Rally, 1972; 1759; 1 box (Box 816)
      - McGovern Speaks-There is a Man, 1972; 1781 c.1-3; 1 box (Box 816)
      - The McGovern Song by Rita Abrams and Ken Melville, 1972; 1782; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Vote McGovern by Aurelio E. Mata and Lew Tobin, 1972; 1783; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Together We Can Win, the Story of George McGovern's Career by Noted Commentator Frank Mankiewicz, 1972; 1784; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Rich Man Plans/Poor Man, 1972; 1785; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Alternative Defense Budget, Press Conference, 1972 January; 1595; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Bethune-Cookman College Speech, 1972 January 1; 167; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Eleanor McGovern on Meet the Press, 1972 January 1; 1366; 1 box (Box 816)
      - McGovern CBS News, 1972 January 3; 24; 1 minute 30 seconds 2-inch color) (Box 816)
      - Press Conferences (Vietnam-POWs), 1972 January 3; 559; 1 box (Box 816)
      - New Hampshire Filing Speech, 1972 January 4; 1309; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Nixon/McGovern, 1972 January 4; 1733; 1 box (Box 816)
      - TV Capsules, 1972 January 6; 156; 1 box (Box 816)
      - University of Arizona Speech, 1972 January 10; 1287; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Dinner Speech, South Phoenix, 1972 January 10; 1291; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Press Conference, Phoenix, 1972 January 10; 1299; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Arizona, CBS TV; "Polls," Bill Moyers NET TV; TV Capsules, Russian/China/JVL/Anderson on Congress, 1972 January 12; 1734; 1 box (Box 816)
      - McGovern, TV, 1972 January 13; 1735; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Eugene McCarthy on Face the Nation and The Democrats CBS News and Senator Muskie on Meet the Press, 1972 January 16; 745; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Boston Press Conference (Scientists), 1972 January 17; 1308; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Senator Nelson, Florida Speech, 1972 January 17; 1571; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Mascenic High School, 1972 January 18; 1295; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Pensacola Speech, 1972 January 19; 753; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Miami Auditorium, McGovern Rally, 1972 January 20; 1 box (Box 816)
        Includes materials with identifiers: 1288, 1289.
      - Florida Tour; Encounter with Bircher, 1972 January 21; 1736; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Agriculture Testimony, 1972 January 24; 1527; 1 box (Box 816)
      - TV Special on Nixon Talk, 1972 January 25; 166; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Nixon North Vietnam Announcement, 1972 January 26; 786; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Machinist Union Speech, Washington D.C., 1972 January 27; 752; 1 box (Box 816)
      - 1972 January 28, 394; 16mm 1 box (Box 816)
      - McGovern, TV: Iowa; CBS, ABC, NBC, 1972 January 25; 1737; 1 box (Box 816)
      - McGovern TV: Nixon Viet Proposal, 1972 January 26; 1738; 1 box (Box 816)
      - "Today," NBC TV; TV News Items, 1972 January 28-30; 1739; 1 box (Box 816)
      - McGovern, TV, 1972 January 31; 1740; 1 box (Box 816)
      - 5 Reports, Boston, CBS, 1972 January 31; 165; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Salem Reception, 1972 January 31; 1306; 1 box (Box 816)
      - McGovern TV: Aid to Education; Second Cut Following Long HHH Cut, 1972 February; 1745; 1 box (Box 816)
      - NET TV Election ’72 Iowa Caucus; ABC TV; WQXR FM, 1972 February 2; 1741; 1 box (Box 816)
      - Franklin Senior Citizens, 1972 February 2; 1303; 1 box (Box 816)
      - KELO-Land-3 Spots, 1972 February 3; 790; 1 box (Box 816)
      - McGovern TV: Others, 1972 February 3-5; 1742; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Korn, Senator McGovern, 1972 February 4; 44; 1 hr 30 minutes 2-inch color) (Box 817)
      - Earth Press Conference, 1972 February 4; 1162; 1 box (Box 817)
      - TV News Items, Xuan Thuy "Face the Nation,", 1972 February 5-6; 1743; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Reaction to Haldeman Statement, 1972 February 7; 794; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Report on Kennedy Spots in New Hampshire, 1972 February 8; 795; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Haldemann Statement, 1972 February 8; 1305; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Exeter Interview-Emergency Health, 1972 February 9-10; 1294; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Senator: Actualities, 1972 February 10-11; 1301; 1 box (Box 817)
      - McGovern TV: CBS; AFL-CIO, Nothing Good, 1972 February 14; 1744; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Drugs-Sanctuary, 1972 February 16; 751; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Claremont, New Hampshire, 1972 February 17; 1318; 1 box (Box 817)
      - Manchester Debate, New Hampshire, 1972 February 18; 1304; 1 box (Box 817)